<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for table tx_drblob_content</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_drblob_content</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:dr_blob/locallang_csh_txdrblobcontent.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
			<label index=".description"></label>
			<label index=".details"></label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="title.description"></label>
			<label index="title.details"></label>
			<label index="type.description"></label>
			<label index="type.details"></label>
			<label index="hidden.description"></label>
			<label index="hidden.details"></label>
			<label index="_hidden.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="starttime.description"></label>
			<label index="_starttime.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="endtime.description"></label>
			<label index="_endtime.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="fe_group.description"></label>
			<label index="_fe_group.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.description"></label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.details"></label>
			<label index="_sys_language_uid.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.description"></label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.details"></label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.description"></label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.details"></label>
			<label index="is_vip.description"></label>
			<label index="is_vip.details"></label>
			<label index="_is_vip.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="description.description"></label>
			<label index="description.details"></label>
			<label index="_description.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="category.description"></label>
			<label index="category.details"></label>
			<label index="_category.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="download_count.description"></label>
			<label index="download_count.details"></label>
			<label index="_download_count.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="blob_name.description"></label>
			<label index="blob_name.details"></label>
			<label index="_blob_name.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="blob_size.description"></label>
			<label index="blob_size.details"></label>
			<label index="_blob_size.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="blob_type.description"></label>
			<label index="blob_type.details"></label>
			<label index="_blob_type.seeAlso"></label>
			<label index="blob_data.description"></label>
			<label index="blob_data.details"></label>
			<label index="_blob_data.seeAlso"></label>
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".description">&quot;Secure Files&quot; are files that are stored either in the database, or in the file system to ensure secure data storage.</label>
			<label index=".details">The Administrator can configure the extension where to store the files uploaded here. You can add meta data to the files and categorize the entries.</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso">tx_drblob_category</label>
			<label index="title.description">Enter a title for this record</label>
			<label index="title.details">The value entered here won't be the filename that is used when downloading the file. This is a mandatory field, so it has to be filled.</label>
			<label index="_title.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_name</label>
			<label index="author.description">Enter an author for this record</label>
			<label index="author.details">This field stores the person in charge for this record to be displayed for website visitors. If not filled in a translated record, the author of the default record will be used</label>
			<label index="_author.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:author_email</label>
			<label index="author_email.description">Enter this record's author's email address</label>
			<label index="author_email.details">This field stores the email address of the person in charge for this record to be displayed for website visitors. If not filled in a translated record, the value of the default record will be used</label>
			<label index="_author_email.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:author</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.description">Version-Flag of the current record</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.details">This field shows up the title of the version of the current file.</label>
			<label index="type.description">Determine whether to store the file in the database or in the filesystem of the server</label>
			<label index="type.details">Both opinions have advantages and disadvantages. Storing the file in the database ensures that the file isn't changed. It also avoids that the file can be recived via URL hacking. Storing the file in the file system is faster, but if the plugin isn't configured correctly the file may be downloaded via URL hacking by non-authorized users.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Set this field to avoid the current record from being shown.</label>
			<label index="_hidden.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:endtime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">The &quot;Start&quot; time determines the date from which the record will be available online.</label>
			<label index="_starttime.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:endtime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">The &quot;End&quot; time determines the date from which the record will NOT be available online anymore.</label>
			<label index="_endtime.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="fe_group.description">Restrict access on this record</label>
			<label index="fe_group.details">If &quot;Access&quot; is set to a usergroup name, only website users which are members of the selected usergroup will be able to view the record when they are logged in. The special option &quot;Hide at login&quot; means this record will NOT be visible for website users that are logged in. Likewise &amp;quot;Show at login&amp;quot; will make entry visible for any logged in frontend user.</label>
			<label index="_fe_group.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:endtime</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.description">The language of the file record.</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.details">This should be the default language unless this record is a translation of another record. Use [ALL] to show the record with every language version.</label>
			<label index="_sys_language_uid.seeAlso">tt_content:sys_language_uid,pages:sys_language_uid,pages_language_overlay:sys_language_uid</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.description">The record in the default language where the current record is a translation from.</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.details">You should not change this field manually because it is handled by the TYPO3 localization system.</label>
			<label index="is_vip.description">Show this record in a &quot;Best-of&quot;-list</label>
			<label index="is_vip.details">This checkbox prepares the record to be shown on the TOP-List of your website. If the hook is not set the record won't be listed in a top list. (Of course the list must be configured to search for records in the current sysfolder)</label>
			<label index="description.description">Enter a description for the file</label>
			<label index="description.details">This field can be used to enter additional information for the file you want offer. </label>
			<label index="category.description">Use this field to categorize a record.</label>
			<label index="category.details">Categorization helps users to find the information they are interested in.</label>
			<label index="_category.seeAlso">tx_drblob_catgegory:title</label>
			<label index="download_count.description">Counts how often the file has been downloaded.</label>
			<label index="download_count.details">This read only field shows the number of times an attached file has been downloaded yet. Use the according button to reset it to zero.</label>
			<label index="blob_name.description">Filename used when downloading the file</label>
			<label index="blob_name.details">This field is filled automatically when a file is uploaded. Enter the filename that is used when the attached file is downloaded after uploading a file. Everytime a file is uploaded for the current record the value of this field will be overwritten by the filename of the uploaded file.</label>
			<label index="_blob_name.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.description">Checksum of the file. Stored automatically.</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.details">This field is filled out automatically. It contains information that may be useful for a person downloding this file to validate its authenticity</label>
			<label index="_blob_checksum.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
			<label index="blob_size.description">Size of the file. Stored automatically.</label>
			<label index="blob_size.details">This field is filled out automatically. It contains information needed by the client browser when downloading the file</label>
			<label index="_blob_size.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
			<label index="blob_type.description">Mimetype of the file. Stored automatically.</label>
			<label index="blob_type.details">This field is filled out automatically. It contains information needed by the client browser when downloading the file</label>
			<label index="_blob_type.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
			<label index="blob_data.description">Select the file you want to attach.</label>
			<label index="blob_data.details">Every record represents a single file, combined with meta information. The file itself can be uploaded using this field. Once the record is saved, the file has been uploaded to the server. You do not need to keep it on your local harddisc.</label>
			<label index="_blob_data.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_name, tx_drblob_content:blob_size, tx_drblob_content:blob_type, tx_drblob_content:blob_checksum</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index=".description">&quot;Sichere Dateien&quot; werden in der Datenbank oder in einem Verzeichnis innerhalb oder außerhalb der TYPO3-Verzeichnisses abgelegt, um eine sichere Datenspeicherung zu gewährleisten.</label>
			<label index=".details">Der Administrator definiert, wo die Dateien gespeichert werden sollen. Den Dateien können Metainformationen und Kategorien hinzugefügt werden.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Geben Sie einen Titel für den Datensatz an.</label>
			<label index="title.details">Der hier angegebene Titel wird nicht dem Dateinamen beim Herunterladen entsprechen; dieser Titel dient der Beschreibung der Datei. Dies ist ein Pflichtfeld und muss angegeben werden.</label>
			<label index="cruser_id.description">Wählen Sie den Benutzer aus, der als Autor des Datensatzes angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="cruser_id.details">Normalerweise wird der Autor eines Datensatzes automatisch gesetzt. Manchmal aber kann es nützlich sein, diesen Wert zu ändern; etwa wenn Sie statt Ihres Kollegen einen Datensatz erstellen.</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.description">Versions-Flag des aktuellen Datensatzes</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.details">Dieses Feld zeigt den Titel der Version der aktuellen Datei.</label>
			<label index="type.description">Legt fest, ob die Datei in der Datenbank oder im Dateisystem des Servers gespeichert werden soll.</label>
			<label index="type.details">Beide Möglichkeiten haben Vor- und Nachteile. Das Speichern der Datei in der Datenbank macht die Datei revisionssicher. Die Datei kann garantiert nicht über URL-Hacking erreicht werden. Das Speichern im Dateisystem ist schneller, es kann jedoch sein, dass bei falsch konfiguriertem Plug-In die Datei von nicht authorisierten Benutzern heruntergeladen werden kann.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Legt fest, ob die Datei für alle Besucher der Web-Site verborgen werden soll.</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">Das &quot;Start&quot;-Datum legt fest, ab wann der Datensatz online sichtbar wird.</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">Das &quot;Stopp&quot;-Datum legt fest, ab welchem Datum der Datensatz &lt;em&gt;nicht&lt;/em&gt; mehr online sichtbar ist.</label>
			<label index="fe_group.description">Zugriffsschutz des Datensatzes</label>
			<label index="fe_group.details">Wenn &quot;Zugriff&quot; mit dem Namen einer Benutzergruppe belegt ist, sind nur Benutzer, die zu dieser Gruppe gehören, in der Lage, den Datensatz zu betrachten bzw. die Datei herunterzuladen, sofern sie angemeldet sind. Die spezielle Option &quot;Nach Anmeldung verbergen&quot; bedeutet, dass der Datensatz angemeldeten Benutzern nicht gezeigt wird. Im Gegensatz werden mit &quot;Anzeigen, wenn angemeldet&quot; markierte Dateien allen angemeldeten Benutzern gezeigt.</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.description">Sprache des aktuellen Datensatzes.</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.details">Falls es sich nicht um eine Übersetzung eines anderen Eintrags handelt, sollte dies die Standardsprache sein. Stellen Sie &quot;[Alle]&quot; ein, damit der Eintrag in allen Sprachen erscheint.</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.description">Der ursprüngliche Eintrag in der Standardsprache, dessen Übersetzung der aktuelle Eintrag ist.</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.details">Dieses Feld sollte nicht manuell geändert werden, da es durch das TYPO3-Lokalisierungssystem verwaltet wird.</label>
			<label index="is_vip.description">Diesen Datensatz in einer &quot;Best-of&quot;-Liste anzeigen</label>
			<label index="is_vip.details">Wenn Sie dieses Feld anklicken, kann diese Datei in einer sog. &quot;Best-of&quot;-Liste erscheinen. Oder anders: Ist der Hacken nicht gesetzt, so wird die Datei niemals in einer &quot;Best-of&quot; erscheinen. (Natürlich muss die Liste so konfiguriert sein, dass der aktuelle Ordner berücksichtigt wird).</label>
			<label index="description.description">Geben Sie eine (detaillierte) Beschreibung der Datei an.</label>
			<label index="description.details">Dieses Feld ist gedacht, um zusätzliche Informationen zur Datei zu hinterlegen, wie z.B. Installation- bzw. Nutzungshinweise, Vorabinformationen usw.</label>
			<label index="category.description">Hier können der aktuellen Datei Kategorien zugewiesen werden.</label>
			<label index="category.details">Kategorisierung hilft den Benutzern, relevante Informationen schneller zu finden.</label>
			<label index="download_count.description">Zähler, wie oft diese Datei bereits heruntergeladen wurde.</label>
			<label index="download_count.details">Dieses schreibgeschützte Feld zeigt an, wie oft eine Datei bereits heruntergeladen wurde. Nutzen Sie die zugehörigen Schaltfläche, um den Wert auf 0 zurückzusetzen.</label>
			<label index="blob_name.description">Dateiname, der erscheint, wenn die Datei heruntergeladen wird.</label>
			<label index="blob_name.details">Dieses Feld wird automatisch ausgefüllt, wenn eine Datei an ein Dokument angehängt wird. Dieses Feld wird jedesmal, wenn eine Datei angehängt wird, automatisch geschrieben. Sollten Sie also den Dateinamen manuell korrigieren wollen, so muss zuerst eine Datei angehängt werden. Sobald der Datensatz gespeichert wurde, kann der Dateiname geändert werden.</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.description">Prüfsumme der angehängten Datei</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.details">Dieses Feld wird automatisch geschrieben und kann nicht geändert werden. Es enthält Information, die es der Person, die diese Datei herunterlädt, ermöglicht, die Authentizität der Datei zu überprüfen.</label>
			<label index="blob_size.description">Größe der angehängten Datei.</label>
			<label index="blob_size.details">Dieses Feld wird automatisch geschrieben und kann nicht geändert werden.</label>
			<label index="blob_type.description">Typ der angehängten Datei.</label>
			<label index="blob_type.details">Dieses Feld wird automatisch geschrieben und kann nicht geändert werden. Es beinhaltet den MIME-Typ der angehängten Datei</label>
			<label index="blob_data.description">Wählen Sie die Datei, die angehängt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="blob_data.details">Jedes Dokument repräsentiert eine Datei (angereichert mit Metainformationen wie Titel, Beschreibung, Kategorien usw.). Sobald ein Datensatz mit angehängter Datei gespeichert wird, wird die Datei auf den Web-Server hochgeladen und muss nicht mehr auf der lokalen Festplatte aufbewahrt werden.</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso">tx_drblob_category</label>
			<label index="_title.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_name</label>
			<label index="_hidden.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:endtime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="_starttime.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:endtime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="_endtime.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:fe_group</label>
			<label index="_fe_group.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:hidden, tx_drblob_content:starttime, tx_drblob_content:endtime, fe_groups</label>
			<label index="_sys_language_uid.seeAlso">tt_content:sys_language_uid,pages:sys_language_uid,pages_language_overlay:sys_language_uid</label>
			<label index="_category.seeAlso">tx_drblob_catgegory:title</label>
			<label index="_blob_name.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
			<label index="_blob_size.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_name, tx_drblob_content:blob_type, tx_drblob_content:blob_size</label>
			<label index="_blob_type.seeAlso">tx_drblob_content:blob_data</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
			<label index=".description">&quot;Files Secure&quot;ไฟล์ที่เก็บไว้ทั้งในฐานข้อมูลหรือระบบไฟล์เพื่อเก็บเป็นข้อมูลความปลอดภัย</label>
			<label index=".details">ผู้ดูแลระบบสามารถกำหนดค่าส่วนขยายที่จัดเก็บไฟล์ที่อัพโหลดที่นี่ คุณสามารถเพิ่มข้อมูล meta ไฟล์และประเภทรายการ</label>
			<label index="title.description">ป้อนชื่อสำหรับบันทึกนี้</label>
			<label index="title.details">ค่าเข้าที่นี่จะไม่ชื่อไฟล์ที่ใช้เมื่อดาวน์โหลดไฟล์ที่ นี้เป็นเขตบังคับจึงต้องได้รับการบรรจุ</label>
			<label index="cruser_id.description">เลือกผู้ใช้ที่ถูกแสดงเป็นผู้เขียนบันทึก</label>
			<label index="cruser_id.details">Normaly ผู้เขียนบันทึกเป็นชุด automatilly แต่ในบางกรณีอาจเป็นประโยชน์เพื่อให้สามารถเปลี่ยนค่านี้เช่นเมื่อคุณสร้างระเบียนแทนเพื่อนร่วมงานของคุณ</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.description">Version - ธงของบันทึกปัจจุบัน</label>
			<label index="t3ver_label.details">ฟิลด์นี้จะปรากฏชื่อของรุ่นของแฟ้มปัจจุบัน</label>
			<label index="type.description">กำหนดว่าจะเก็บไฟล์ในฐานข้อมูลหรือระบบไฟล์ของเซิร์ฟเวอร์</label>
			<label index="type.details">ความคิดเห็นทั้งสองมีข้อดีและข้อเสีย การจัดเก็บไฟล์ในฐานข้อมูลเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าไฟล์ไม่ถูกเปลี่ยน นอกจากนี้ยังหลีกเลี่ยงที่ไฟล์สามารถ recived ผ่านทาง URL hacking การเก็บแฟ้มในระบบแฟ้มที่เร็ว แต่ถ้าปลั๊กอินไม่ได้กำหนดค่าอย่างถูกต้องไฟล์อาจจะดาวน์โหลดผ่านทาง URL hacking โดยผู้ใช้ไม่อนุญาต</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">ตั้งค่าฟิลด์นี้เพื่อหลีกเลี่ยงการบันทึกปัจจุบันจากการแสดง</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">&quot;เวลา&quot;เริ่มจากกำหนดวันที่บันทึกจะสามารถออนไลน์</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">End&quot;&quot;เวลากำหนดวันที่ซึ่งบันทึกจะไม่สามารถใช้ได้อีกต่อไปออนไลน์</label>
			<label index="fe_group.description">จำกัด การเข้าถึงในบันทึกนี้</label>
			<label index="fe_group.details">ถ้า&quot;Access&quot;ตั้งชื่อ usergroup เฉพาะผู้ใช้เว็บไซต์ที่เป็นสมาชิกของ usergroup ที่เลือกจะสามารถดูบันทึกเมื่อมีการเข้าสู่ระบบค่ะตัวเลือกพิเศษ&quot;ซ่อนที่เข้าสู่ระบบ&quot;หมายถึงการบันทึกจะมองไม่เห็นนี้ ผู้ใช้เว็บไซต์ที่มีการเข้าระบบเช่นเดียวกัน&quot;แสดงที่เข้า&quot;จะปรากฏสำหรับผู้ใช้เข้าสู่ระบบ frontend ใด</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.description">ภาษาของการบันทึกไฟล์</label>
			<label index="sys_language_uid.details">นี้ควรจะเป็นภาษาเริ่มต้นนอกจากนี้การแปลบันทึกของบันทึกอื่น ใช้ [ALL] แสดงบันทึกกับทุกรุ่นภาษา</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.description">บันทึกในภาษาเริ่มต้นที่บันทึกปัจจุบันคือการแปลจาก</label>
			<label index="l18n_parent.details">คุณไม่ควรเปลี่ยนช่องเองเพราะระบบจัดการโดยท้องถิ่น TYPO3 นี้</label>
			<label index="is_vip.description">แสดงบันทึกนี้ใน&quot;Best - รายการ&quot;-</label>
			<label index="is_vip.details">ช่องทำเครื่องหมายนี้จัดทำระเบียนแสดงในรายการ TOP - ของเว็บไซต์ของคุณ ถ้าขอไม่ได้ตั้งบันทึกจะไม่ปรากฏในรายชื่อด้านบน (แน่นอนรายการจะต้องกำหนดค่าให้ค้นหาระเบียนใน sysfolder ปัจจุบัน)</label>
			<label index="description.description">ป้อนคำอธิบายไฟล์</label>
			<label index="description.details">ฟิลด์นี้สามารถใช้ในการป้อนข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมสำหรับแฟ้มที่คุณต้องการให้</label>
			<label index="category.description">ใช้ฟิลด์นี้ประเภทบันทึก</label>
			<label index="category.details">หมวดหมู่ช่วยให้ผู้ใช้ที่จะหาข้อมูลพวกเขาสนใจ</label>
			<label index="download_count.description">นับความถี่แฟ้มได้รับการดาวน์โหลด</label>
			<label index="download_count.details">นี้อ่านข้อมูลเท่านั้นแสดงจำนวนครั้งที่ไฟล์ที่แนบมาได้ถูกดาวน์โหลดยัง ใช้ปุ่มตามที่ตั้งค่าให้เป็นศูนย์</label>
			<label index="blob_name.description">Filename ใช้เมื่อดาวน์โหลดไฟล์</label>
			<label index="blob_name.details">ฟิลด์นี้จะเต็มไปโดยอัตโนมัติเมื่อมีการอัพโหลดไฟล์ ป้อนชื่อไฟล์ที่ใช้เมื่อมีการดาวน์โหลดไฟล์ที่แนบมาหลังจากอัปโหลดไฟล์ ทุกไฟล์จะถูกอัปโหลดสำหรับบันทึกปัจจุบันค่าของเขตข้อมูลนี้จะถูกแทนที่โดยชื่อของไฟล์ที่อัพโหลด</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.description">Checksum ของไฟล์ จัดเก็บโดยอัตโนมัติ</label>
			<label index="blob_checksum.details">ฟิลด์นี้จะกรอกโดยอัตโนมัติ มันมีข้อมูลที่อาจมีประโยชน์สำหรับคน downloding file นี้เพื่อตรวจสอบความถูกต้องของ</label>
			<label index="blob_size.description">ขนาดของไฟล์ จัดเก็บโดยอัตโนมัติ</label>
			<label index="blob_size.details">เขตนี้กรอกโดยอัตโนมัติ มันมีข้อมูลที่จำเป็นโดยเบราว์เซอร์ลูกค้าเมื่อดาวน์โหลดไฟล์</label>
			<label index="blob_type.description">Mimetype ของไฟล์ จัดเก็บโดยอัตโนมัติ</label>
			<label index="blob_type.details">ฟิลด์นี้จะกรอกโดยอัตโนมัติ มันมีข้อมูลที่จำเป็นโดยเบราว์เซอร์ลูกค้าเมื่อดาวน์โหลดไฟล์</label>
			<label index="blob_data.description">เลือกไฟล์ที่คุณต้องการแนบ</label>
			<label index="blob_data.details">ทุกบันทึกเป็นไฟล์เดียวรวมกับข้อมูลเมตา file ตัวเองสามารถอัพโหลดใช้ข้อมูลนี้ เมื่อบันทึกจะถูกบันทึกไฟล์จะถูกอัพโหลดไปยังเซิร์ฟเวอร์ คุณไม่จำเป็นต้องเก็บไว้ใน harddisc ท้องถิ่นของคุณ</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>